http://www.dkgnet.com/privacy-policy-2/

Client File Upload Utility
Privacy PolicyWe have plans and options to fit just about anyone's budget.
You are here:  Home › Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement
DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com collects basic client information to make your support experience the very best on the Internet. We respect your privacy, and we assure you that we will maintain and use this information responsibly.
General Browsing:
DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com gathers navigational information about where you go on our Web site. This information allows us to see which areas of DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com are most visited. This helps us improve the quality of visitors’ online shopping experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our Web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).
Disclosure of Personal Information:
Any information you provide to us at this site when you establish or update an account, purchase credits online or request information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information), is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com to deliver services to you. To ensure compliance with federal law, DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com does not maintain information provided by children under the age of 16.
You should be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Web site, the site or the public.
DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com does not sell, rent or trade your e-mail address to third parties. We may, however, use third parties to help us provide services to you, such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, and administering e-mails. If personally identifiable information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number) is provided to any of these third parties, we will require that such information be maintained by them in strictest confidence.
Use of Cookies:
DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com to make our site more responsive to your needs, by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and are used by DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com to help track your clicks as you go through the pages within DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com Web site. In addition, DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com uses cookies to help keep track of support requests and to tell us whether you have previously visited DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site.
Updating Personal Information:
We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information including billing and shipping information by logging into your account.
Links:
For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other sites. DKGNET.com and DKGHosting.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Questions/Changes in Policy:
If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. If elements of our Privacy Policy change, we will post the policy changes in our Privacy Policy on this Web site. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about DKGnet.com and DKGHosting.com.
Security Statement
DKGNnet.com and DKGHosting.com believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our clients. We provide stringent and effective security measures on our Web site.
It is our policy to never send private information, such as your credit card number, via e-mail. In fact, this is a practice we recommend you adopt in all of your Internet activities.
search this site
Quick Jump:
